<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All Chapters on SYMBIOSIS</title>
    <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in All Chapters on SYMBIOSIS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Outro</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/outro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/outro/</guid>
      <description>“The texts labeled ‘history’ tell one story. If anyone bothers to ask, we can tell another.”
This Ks’ou, who should have been his enemy, said these words as she shifted her weight on the edge of the vault of their damaged ship, then pushed one of the last bottles of water in his direction. It rolled to him easily. He picked it up and tried to suppress the hint of disgust as he drank, but he could not help the display, obvious as a Human grimace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 (Kelisfton)</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>“Flesh describes an alien entity, a more or less expendable figure…
its most poignant determination is the extent to which such a body cannot prevent or ward off another&amp;rsquo;s touch. The single-most powerful evidence of the loss of freedom is the fact that bodies lose their integrity and may be &amp;gt;invaded or entered… by coercive power. This touch that we associate with intimacy… becomes instead the power to wound and violate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Previous Chapter
NeVarr&amp;ndash;and by default, James&amp;ndash;were standing in front of the tank. The edges on the wide afro of the human glowing slightly aquamarine in its light. The Ks&amp;rsquo;ou formed the humans lips and sent the signals to vibrate the throat: it was a quiet mumble, as they shook a flaky substance onto the open top of the water. A couple of snails were stuck to the side of the tank; the fish that remained from the last fiasco were maneuvering calmly throughout the seagrass that NeVarr had recently planted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2*</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-2star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-2star/</guid>
      <description>Previous Chapter
Ana Joseph and Aurana~
Spring PsKE 39, 2—-
Dr. Hagåtña
A Brief History of Human Colonization
‘Chronotope’ (Time-Space) is a theory by the ancient Russian thinker M. M. Bakhtin (citation needed). He argues that Narration can be looked at separately through the lense of these two different relationships: temporal (time) and spatial (space). These two components express a particular worldview or ideology depending on the genre of literature you find it in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Previous Chapter
Not all heroes die in a fantastic blaze of light.
Some die quite normally, with facility. Closed eyes and a simple, unperturbed decision to shift, to decay into the next mode of being.
Suddenly, in the middle of the night, from a lung that refuses to fill, or a heart that refuses to beat, organs consumed by the slow burn of existence.
Some die in the dark, alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4 (Kelisfton)</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/symbiosisnovel/chapters/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>“One cannot ‘unsettle’ the ‘coloniality of power’ without a redescription of the human—
a redescription of the human outside of the terms of our present descriptive statement of the human.
The human: Man, and its overrepresentation.1”
Sylvia Wynter
&amp;ndash;
 Previous Chapter
You have discovered inhabitable planets, at least, those inhabitable by your standards. You have wondered how long it will take to travel there. You have questioned why alien species who might live there have not reached out to you; made contact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>